http://www.gracemoore.net/policy.htm

Privacy Statement for
GraceMoore.net
GraceMoore.net
has created this privacy
statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses the information gathering and
dissemination practices for this Web site:
GraceMoore.net
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information.
Cookies
Our Site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.
Advertisers
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies.
While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are
collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Personal Information
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally
identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.
Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal
information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites.
GraceMoore.net
is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
webmaster@gracemoore.net
